Do you have cash?
I didn't bring any cash.
The world is full of coincidences.
You can add hers with mine.
No, you don't have to.
Twenty years ago,
I had a fateful encounter with Mariko.
I've always just watched over her.
But now, she is finally aware of me.
NOTICE OF TRANSFER
Coincidences can be manufactured.
A coincidence meant to make Mariko smile.
That old retro-style cafe
behind the office?
However…
there are plenty of people who
approach Mariko and those who envy her.
I have evidence that you used fraud
to obtain that partnership.
If you don't want this exposed,
withdraw from the new project.
Please, withdraw.
-Please!
-What is wrong with you?
Are you crazy or something?
-Whoa!
-Please!
I must do what I need to do.
Murder?
Because I'm the one by Mariko's side.
I'M THE ONLY ONE BY MARIKO'S SIDE
I'll protect her.
19-JUN-26
That is the one thing I won't compromise.
NOSE COSMETICS
8:23 a.m.
Mariko goes to work
at this exact time every morning.
BRAND BUSINESS DEPARTMENT
-Good morning.
The very first thing she does when she
arrives at work is use alcohol sanitizer.
After thoroughly wiping the keyboard,
she checks the day's schedule,
right about now.
TOKYO DEPARTMENT STORE STATUS
Once she finishes that…
Here you go.
Thank you. I was just
thinking I wanted one.
Mariko likes café lattes.
I know everything about Mariko.
PROPOSAL TO INTRODUCE AI
INTO CLOUD SERVICES
If we introduce AI into the cloud system,
the work required to find documents
from our vast library
should decrease significantly.
No, to put that into effect,
-the cost would be enormous--
-That is exactly
the kind of thing
we should spend money on.
If we revamp the system,
it should reduce overtime by 40 hours
per year in each department.
That's easy for her to say.
From her standpoint, yes.
I heard she just got
a new project approved too.
Must be nice to have someone
backing you up.
Don't worry about what they say.
Oh, that.
-I'm used to it.
-What?
Wait, so are you still sad
about that thing?
I never imagined dating would be harder
than college or job-hunting.
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
I can't even keep a text conversation
going with anyone.
In the end, they just want to get
on good terms with my father.
A lot of them are like that.
So they're not actually interested in you?
Don't put it so bluntly.
What about that guy from the other day?
The one your grandmother
introduced to you.
I almost didn't come.
But I'm glad I came.
What about his job? What does he do?
Uh, he's a civil servant.
A civil servant! That's great!
-You think so?
-Yes!
But we have had no developments
since then, either.
Mariko, maybe you're not taking
any initiative at all?
Are you making an effort to show them
who you really are?
I plan to do it…
Don't just plan, do it!
Hello.
-Hello.
-Hey there.
Mariko, you can make it tomorrow, right?
To the golf session with the CEO
of Keihin Department Store.
-Yes.
-Actually,
I received a call from them
just a moment ago.
It seems one of them can't make it.
Then shall we send
another one on our side?
Asai, can you go?
-No, I'm not really good at golf.
-Mariko started golfing after she joined.
It's good for entertaining guests.
Mariko always prepares
so that nothing at work
can catch her by surprise.
You still can't contact Tateiwa?
No.
What's going on?
And…
I have my preparations too.
NOSE COSMETICS
Sorry for bothering you.
I'd like to speak with
the person in charge here.
Please wait a moment. I'll ask.
Well then, what can we help you with?
Last night, around 10 p.m.,
one of your directors,
Mr. Tsuyoshi Tateiwa,
was found dead.
What?
Was it an accident?
The police are investigating it
as a criminal case.
When was the last time
you contacted Mr. Tateiwa?
Two days ago.
Actually, we were unable
to reach him as well, and we were worried.
By the way, did Mr. Tateiwa
have any trouble at work,
or did anyone hold grudges against him?
This email was sent to me
the night before yesterday.
This is evidence
that Tateiwa was misappropriating
company expenses and other funds.
-Do you have any idea who the sender is?
-I do not.
The night two days ago,
that would be when the murder occurred.
-May we have this data?
-Yes.
We would also like to see
Mr. Tateiwa's desk.
-Asai.
-Yes.
-I'll show you.
-Thank you.
This is terrible! This is terrible! Hey!
-The police are here!
-What?
The police?
They say Mr. Tateiwa
was murdered.
-What? What do you mean he was murdered?
-No…
I don't know the details, but…
Look, the detectives are here.
Last night, at around 10 p.m.,
a man was found collapsed on the street
and was confirmed to have passed away.
The incident happened after 5:00 p.m.
A passerby reported
finding a man collapsed
on a street in Shinagawa.
The victim was Mr. Tsuyoshi Tateiwa.
His body had several stab wounds,
and the police are investigating this
as a homicide.
TSUYOSHI TATEIWA
CREATING BACKUP
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO RESET THIS PC?
RESETTING PC…
SATORU HATANO RELEASED FROM PRISON
If there is anything else
you wish to investigate,
please contact me directly.
Understood. Thank you very much.
Good day.
Those incriminating documents,
sent anonymously…
I'd bet they were sent by the killer.
COMPANY DIRECTOR FOUND DEAD ON STREET
DEEMED HOMICIDE
Here, this is on the house.
You don't seem to be focusing
very well on your work today.
Thank you very much.
You're that guy's boss, right?
-That guy?
-Sota Yukimura.
Yes. Are you acquaintances?
Yes, yes, we both
went to Futasubashi University.
-Futasubashi, I went there too.
-Oh, here he is.
Hey, don't say anything you don't need to.
It's fine. She'd find out
eventually anyway.
We were both in the Faculty of Commerce.
I went there too!
We both took a gap year, so we're
one academic year below you, though.
-Oh, really?
-I've wanted to talk to you
ever since university.
Oh, I'm Tomoya Sagara, by the way.
-Okay.
-Mariko, what do you think of this guy--
That's enough.
-What, what?
-Go back to work.
I'm going, all right, all right.
I get it, okay? Want a cookie?
No.
Don't be mad. I said I was sorry.
I was trying to be your wingman,
giving you two a chance
to get to know each other.
Look, consider this an apology.
You liar. Bet you just talked
and couldn't stop.
It's fine.
I know what's okay to say and what's not.
If I told her you've loved her
for 25 years straight,
she'd find it creepy
and reject you instantly.
I would absolutely never say that.
Don't worry.
I won't steal your one and only love.
What? Mariko wouldn't
fall for you, Tomoya.
What's that about? You don't know that.
I know everything about Mariko.
Everything, huh…
Well then, do you know
who Mariko's closest friend is?
Her colleague and secretary, Izumi.
That was fast.
Izumi is a senior colleague
three years older than Mariko,
but since Mariko is the manager,
she is her most trusted subordinate.
While they have
a professional relationship,
she is a rare, friend-like figure
with whom Mariko can be herself.
Then what about outside of work?
Like how she spends
long holidays and stuff.
Mariko doesn't take much paid leave…
Oh, but for New Year's, she spent it
in London with her grandmother.
You could see fireworks
from the Thames River cruise.
They were beautiful.
Did you go too…
No, never mind.
I don't really want to know. It's scary.
When it comes to Mariko, I know
everything, and I understand everything.
I wonder.
-What?
-This all sounds very one-sided to me.
Would she really date you?
What?
-I'm not planning on--
-And what's that you've been doing?
Golf?
MARIKO
Nice shot!
-Sent it flying, like always!
-All right!
-Nice shot!
-Your direction is perfect!
Thank you very much.
Do you have a professional coach?
I went to a place called Koto Golf Club.
I used to go there too.
Oh, it's nice there, isn't it?
It's close to the company,
and they offer cheap personal lessons.
That's true.
Man, where do you train, Jinno?
Sorry for asking you
to come on such short notice.
No one else in our department
could play golf, so it was a huge help.
Not at all.
Do you play often?
I often go to the driving range
at Koto Golf Club.
I wonder if a lot of people
from our company go there?
That might be the case.
Playing golf with Mariko…
To think such a day would come.
Am I about to be called to heaven? No,
perhaps I have already been called.
This is heaven.
Nice shot!
I think this one would be better.
Thank you.
-Nice one!
To think such a day would come…
Isn't your company
having it rough right now?
You know, with that director,
Tateiwa, was it?
Yes.
We pulled some strings to keep
the company name out of the news for now.
Well, the weekly magazines
will probably find out eventually, though.
Well,
a murder case is no laughing matter.
It'd be terrifying if the killer
turned out to be someone close to him.
Yes, exactly.
Thankfully, our brand for young people
called VELEL is performing well.
I know. I saw an article saying that
while the industry as a whole
is struggling to establish brand loyalty,
VELEL has maintained
an upward trend since its release.
Actually, it has been decided
that we will be launching
a new skincare line from VELEL.
We would be very grateful to have
your support, Jinno.
Shall we set up
an independent counter at our place?
Yes, please!
Your father and I
have been friends for over half a century,
so our department store
will give you full support.
Thank you very much.
My, how impressive, how impressive.
Nose Cosmetics is secure
with such a splendid successor.
Well,
I only made her a director
because she's my daughter.
She still has a long way to go.
You've known each other for over 50 years.
What relationship do you have?
We're in a Gin-chan,
Jin-chan kind of friendship.
That's right.
I didn't think Jin-chan
would rise this high, though.
Well, I'm glad we stayed on good terms.
The feeling is mutual.
Just this way.
You did great, Jin-chan.
-Thank you for today.
-Likewise.
Great work. Thank you for today.
Let's meet again.
Yes. Thank you very much.
-Well then, I'll be leaving.
-Okay.
See you.
Yukimura, I'll give you a ride.
What?
You must be tired, right?
-Sorry, I know it's your day off.
-No, no.
That's not why.
At what age did you start drinking coffee?
That was a boring question. Sorry.
Um…
I think it was in elementary school?
I think I snuck a sip of what
my mother was drinking.
Oh, but I didn't start liking it
until I became an adult.
-I like cafes, so that's why.
-Oh,
I like cafes too.
Um, I like how you're in the same space,
but it feels like everyone
is in their own world.
-I get that. I feel the same way.
-Oh?
You do?
Well, ever since I was a kid,
I've liked looking at apartment buildings
from a distance.
Apartment buildings?
When those concrete-enclosed boxes
are born into this world,
people who were living separate lives
fit neatly and politely into them.
In that collective nature,
I felt a kind of beauty.
That same feeling
is packed into cafes too.
No one knows each other,
but in the way that everyone
gathers in a single space
and quietly shares time together,
I feel a sense of romance.
I'm talking too much, aren't I?
I don't mind.
Sorry.
We surprisingly have a lot in common.
Same university, too.
Yes, uh, well, I barely managed
to slip in after a gap year.
I barely got in too.
But for some reason,
I've had a lucky life.
Even on the day of the entrance exam,
I messed up,
but I got lucky and passed.
I don't think it was luck.
You studied so hard.
It was your own ability.
I mean, you just lost
your exam admission ticket.
It doesn't mean you'd fail, right?
What? Did I mention a ticket?
No, uh…
I just figured, messing up on exam day
would mean losing
or dropping your exam ticket.
Oh, okay.
In other words, what I wanted to say
is that both university
and your current job
are results you grabbed
through real effort…
and not luck at all.
Sorry for speaking like I know everything.
Everyone else says differently, though.
Well, I only get to see clients
because my father is backing me up.
So I don't blame them.
I wonder why I'm telling you this.
It's fine.
July 25th.
Today, several things that should
have been impossible, no,
things I've always waited for,
have finally happened.
JULY 25
It makes me realize
that life is connected.
Because I started playing golf back then,
it led to me being invited
to the client game today.
MARIKO
FIRST TIME PLAYING GOLF IN A WHILE
THE WEATHER WAS GREAT
But…
if life is connected…
JAPONICA WORKBOOK
…then it's possible…
that the past will catch up with you.
Today,
I overheard something outrageous.
You got me good today, Jin-chan!
Oh, by the way,
I heard Hatano was released
from prison, right?
Yes…
Him, kidnapping someone…
I still can't believe it.
It looks like he's telling the weekly mags
lots of things.
Be careful.
It was a long time ago, but he might talk
about you too.
This man named Hatano…
SERIAL KIDNAPPER, 1 DEATH
Somebody! Somebody help!
-Though Mariko's kidnapping was thwarted,
-No! No!
he kidnapped five other children
and murdered one who tried to escape.
WEAPON CONFISCATED AT HOME
HATANO SENTENCED TO 25 YEARS
It was reported that
he stated he targeted children
of wealthy families,
GINJIRO NOSE
but Mariko's father and the kidnapper
were originally acquaintances.
That shouldn't have been
written anywhere, and yet…
The President covered it up?
WHY AN INDEPENDENT COUNTER AT KEIHIN?
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW WITH SATORU HATANO
SERIAL KIDNAPPER RELEASED AFTER 25 YEARS
THE DECIDING POINT IN THE GAME
Eight, huh?
MAN FOUND DEAD ON STREET IN SHINAGAWA
NOSE COSMETICS
I'm from Drip & Note.
-Right this way.
-Thank you.
Excuse me.
Have we met somewhere before?
Ah, sorry, sorry.
Not trying to flirt, really.
Um…
Do you need something?
There's something stuck there…
Thank you.
It's cute, though.
What? Yukimura went golfing
with the president?
Yes.
The president was very pleased.
He said he was really good and attentive.
That's surprising for Yukimura.
He seems quiet. So he's on "that side".
What do you mean, "that side"?
The side that thinks
about promotions and stuff.
It's not so easy for an ordinary employee
to get into the president's good graces.
So, he got in through golf. I see, I see.
Why don't you do golf too then, Sano?
What? I have no interest in golf.
Promotions are a hassle anyway.
What's with you?
I mean, it's tough, right?
Manager? Is something wrong?
Nothing.
Ah, let me get that.
Thanks.
-Hello.
Did something happen with Mariko?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I'm Sakura.
Um, we met the other day.
-I'm sorry.
-No, no.
I didn't mean to startle you.
It's fine…
I scared you the other day too, didn't I?
You were that detective, right?
Yes.
I was too vague,
saying I'm a civil servant.
I'm sorry.
Of course you can't reveal everything
to someone you just met.
Um…
Can we start over?
My name is Taisuke Sakura.
I work at the Metropolitan
Police Department, Division One.
Twenty years of service.
I am single.
I was hoping to deepen
my acquaintance with you,
Mariko, in my private life.
If you'd like,
how about we have
a meal together sometime?
What?
That's not what we agreed on!
I want our brand to be placed
at an independent counter
at Keihin Department Store.
If it's lumped together with Nose Brand
counters, we'll take customers from--
It's not a bad thing
for the company as a whole.
It will also help acquire
new customers for the existing brands.
VELEL has a different target demographic
from our other brands.
If they are placed side by side,
our brand image will be indecisive!
I cannot give you special treatment.
Special treatment?
Did this project pass
because I'm the president's daughter?
This project passed
because I'm the president's daughter.
I became manager
because I'm your daughter.
I only got into this company
And because I'm your daughter,
I got kidnapped.
Mariko may be the president's daughter,
but she isn't relying
on special treatment.
Mariko has been fighting forever.
Mariko, hold on.
Wait.
I'll be fine by myself.
The culprit has been caught.
-But…
-I'm off.
Mariko…
Even though she must have been hurt a lot…
she always looked forward…
and fought with her own strength.
It has nothing to do with being
the president's daughter.
Mariko is Mariko…
Nobody understands.
Because I know the real Mariko.
So what if you do?
Just knowing doesn't
change anything, does it?
What do you want to do?
You've loved her for 25 years,
but never had the courage to talk to her.
You've just always watched.
Now you've finally talked to her,
and she's aware of you, right?
So what next?
COSMETICS INGREDIENT GUIDELINE
VELEL SKINCARE - SEPARATE PR CAMPAIGN
SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING
CHANCE OF SUCCESS, HIGH
Sorry.
This is…
Um, uh, well…
It would be great if we could have
an independent counter
at Keihin Department Store,
but I realized that
we didn't originally think up
the PR plan based on that assumption.
So I looked into
the PR methods used by
hit products in recent years.
EXPERIENCE BOOTH AT TRAIN STATIONS
If we use a selling method
that goes against our intentions
and causes the concept of VELEL
to be conveyed incorrectly to the world,
taking a slow and steady approach
might be the better option.
Ah, but it would mean going
against the president's wishes,
so that might cause trouble
for you, Manager…
I misunderstood you.
I thought you
just wanted my father to like you
to advance your career.
That's why you were working hard
in this department and being nice to me.
But…
you actually have pure intentions.
I'm the one
who assumed everyone only cares about me
because I'm the president's daughter.
I failed to actually look at you
as a person.
I'm sorry.
Actually, I was thinking
the exact same thing.
A PR method suited for VELEL…
I want to help!
I want to help
and be by your side, Manager.
I'm so surprised that a time
like this would come in my life,
and it's so unbelievable,
but I'm happy just to be here right now.
That's why I want to work hard.
Being able to be here
makes me the happiest
I've ever been in my life.
What…
"Happiest in your life"?
What an exaggeration…
But…
Thank you.
I want to be of use to Mariko.
Just so that Mariko can live pleasantly
and happily.
That's all.
UNIVERSITY ENTRANCE EXAM SITE
That's all I want.
ENTRANCE EXAM ADMISSION TICKET
Hey, you!
You dropped this.
Thank you very much.
I want to be of use to Mariko.
GINJIRO NOSE
HIDEO JINNO
These two have been together
for more than half a century,
but they both went
to different high schools
and universities.
Which means, they go back
further than that…
HIDEO JINNO
SEE ALL PHOTOS
WITH GIN-CHAN IN OUR OLD HANGOUT
FIRST TIME IN A WHILE!
HOSEN
-Thank you!
-See you!
-Take care! Thank you!
-Thank you!
All right.
All right, all right.
Excuse me.
Yes?
This is all I have…
Wow, thank you so much.
I had no idea Nose's son
had grown this big.
And you're planning
a surprise celebration?
He'd be so happy!
I wonder if I have
anything else interesting?
Wait there a second!
Oh, thank you so much.
YEAR 6, CLASS ONE - FRIENDS FOREVER
HIDEO JINNO
GINJIRO NOSE
YEAR 6, CLASS 2
SEE YOU AGAIN AT THE GRADUATION PARTY
YEAR 6, CLASS 3
NO. 1 GOLD STAR CLASS
Satoru…
SATORU HATANO
Mariko's kidnapping was not a coincidence.
I won't forgive anyone who jeopardizes…
Mariko's happiness.
METROPOLITAN POLICE
It's strange that the camera
has one blind spot
exactly where the crime scene is.
Hey, look.
This is right in front of the crime scene.
Taken right before
the estimated time of death.
Who is this man?
Excuse me.
You're Sota Yukimura, right?
May I speak with you for a moment?
I want Mariko to be happy.
That's all.
So,
you don't need to know anything.
NEXT TIME…
Subtitle translation by: Maslin Friedman